If you are a bike rider and you
have a bike taxi and you drive a bike taxi, then
come, this video is
absolutely 100% very useful for you, so if you
ever meet with an
accident while riding a bike taxi, then
how will you claim for it or
how will you claim for health insurance, we have told you all this
in detail and from here you will
get 100% money, so
first of all what you will have to do is
watch the entire video without skipping
and if you are new to this channel, then
subscribe and motivate by giving a like,
so come on my mobile screen,
there we have told you in full detail, so after
talking about the video,
watch the entire video,
after clicking on the icon, you will
go to the last option in help, which is in help,
after clicking on help, you can see
accident insurance here, so click here, it is
clearly written here,
this is 30000 of hospital and five black  So
if you guys have some optical problem, that is,
if you fall with your bike and you get hurt,
something breaks on your hand, anything happens, then it is
written here and there for the film that
your Tap
Film Insurance Submit,
so this thing is absolutely 100% charged, so you will
not get any option to claim from here, so what
you will have to do in this,
first of all you will have to
go to the Play Store, so first of all
we go to the Play Store,
after going to the Play Store, you will have to
wait a little, after that you will have to search here
ACO
XCOM Aqua, go and click on it,
after that you will have to install your A app, so I have
already
installed it, after that I have also logged in, so
let's open it,
after opening, in your Rapido number, that is, the
mobile number registered in Rapido number, prove that number here,
after that you will definitely get
such an interface, if you
click a little, then below you will see
Rapid and Right Rapid and in the right hand you
go and click and your A app will be installed
here  There will be a lot of dead sleep, okay,
if you have an accident and your hand gets
broken or something
[music]
means the date on which you have the accident, you should do it exactly because
when you people verify the claim, there is a
little problem, so please do it exactly on the correct
date, I had filed your claim on the 25th, I had an
accident on the 25th in Salt Lake Sector 5,
so I filed a claim here,
see,
after doing this here, I had filed
a claim, after that I had filed it,
after that
I took all my reports etc. and
we submitted it here,
after that again
[music] you will do an
accident, click on that date,
after that you people will come to an interface like this,
okay, so click there,
OPD treatment, OPD treatment means that
you people fell while riding your bike, you got a
little injury or you need to do something like X-ray,
then you can get that done in some
good nursing home or something from here  There is
some experience as well, get the
treatment done from there very well
because
what happens is that this Rapido will
refund you the entire money in 14 or 15 days,
so we told you in the last of the video, so what will have to be done, so the
second
option is your overnight hospital, if you have to
stay in the hospital or if
you have to get admitted in the hospital or
some emergency, then you will be admitted in the hospital,
no problem, 2 days, 3 days, no
problem, but keep in mind that
people have not seen more than 30 thousand people, so by doing this you will
make a bill without doing it, okay, and
everything is correct, the documents are correct, if the
documents are not correct, then you will
not get the claim at all and the third
option is permanent handicapped and disabled,
what are permanent handicapped, if
you fall, I mean sorry, you fell, I mean your leg
broke and anything got broken, so this
claim will be given to you, so go to the OPD and
wait a little after clipping,
after that you people, I mean my name has come
here, it is okay, then click on the name, name
After clicking on it, you will get an
interface like this, my mobile number is
showing here and your gender, builder,
choose absolutely everything here,
after that click on continue,
so here
is my self
[music]
I have selected the date of birth,
after that click on continue, after that
see from which region did you
come to claim here, go and
click on it, you had an accident in a bike accident
and the name and hospital or any doctor is not
visible there, I have selected
one of yours,
after clicking on it, I
clicked on continue, sorry continue, whatever is there in
yours is written here,
go and submit it here,
submit the medicine bill there,
if there is no medicine bill,
go to a white paper and see the
name of this medicine, write its
price, after that take a photo and put it
in it, after that go to the medical
prescription which the doctor
gave you, go and click there, if
you have done it again then you
can also put a copy of it in it  But
if it is not there then you cannot put it,
if you have done your scan, whatever
report you have got, do it
[music]
after that your claim will be 100%
successful,
if
you clean the claim then after taking your time there, I
mean see here, I have filed the claim
on 27th April, okay, it has
not been long recently, so there is one claim of
yours, it will remain like this, after that this claim
review option will be
clean here, after that the payment,
after the claim review is successful,
you will get the payment within five to seventy working days, there will be no
problem,
so I hope you guys liked this video very much,
if you like the video then share it,
this is your friend, we are going to the other captain, if
everything is fine then bye
good night for now and do not forget to like the video
and if you are new to this channel then
definitely subscribe,
many such technical videos related to rapid loan will
come